<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<text>   
<Quran>
<strong>LET US COME TOGETHER ON WHAT WE HAVE IN COMMON</strong><br/>
                "O people of the Book! Let us come together on what is common between us and you: 
                that we shall worship none but God; that we shall not associate any partners with Him; 
                (and) that we shall not take from among ourselves any lords other than God."
               <strong>The Holy Quran, 3:64   </strong>
</Quran>

<Quran>
And when it is said to them, "Come towards what Allah has sent down and towards the Noble Messenger", they say, "Sufficient for us is what we found our forefathers upon." Even if their forefathers did not have knowledge nor had guidance?
 <strong>[Surah Al-Maida 5:104]</strong>
</Quran>

<Quran>
And when you are greeted with a greeting, greet [in return] with one better than it or [at least] return it [in a like manner]. Indeed, Allah is ever, over all things, an Accountant.
 <strong>[The Holy Quran, 4:86]</strong>
</Quran>

<Quran>
Among His signs are the night and the day, as well as the sun and the moon: (Therefore) do not worship the sun or the moon, but worship God, who has created them both -- if it is Him whom you (truly) worship.
 <strong>[The Holy Quran, 41:37]</strong>
</Quran>

<Quran>
O humankind! Worship your Guardian-Lord, who created you and those who came before you, that you may have the chance to learn righteousness.
 <strong>[The Holy Quran, 2:21]</strong>
</Quran>

<Quran>
And among them are those who listen to you, but We have placed over their hearts 
coverings, lest they understand it, and in their ears deafness. And if they 
should see every sign, they will not believe in it. Even when they come to you 
arguing with you, those who disbelieve say, "This is not but legends of the former peoples."
<strong>The Holy Quran, Surah Al-Anam 6:25   </strong>
</Quran>

<Quran>
It is He Who has made you (His) agents, inheritors of the earth: He has raised you in ranks, some above others: that 
He may try you in the gifts He has given you: for your Lord is quick in punishment: yet He is indeed Oft-forgiving, Most Merciful. 
<strong>[Surah Al-Anam 6:165]</strong>
</Quran>

<Hadith>
<strong>Give Food & Greet Everyone</strong><br/>
Abdullah bin Amr bin Al-as (May Allah be pleased with them) reported: A man asked the Messenger of Allah (PBUH): "Which act in Islam is the best?" He (PBUH) replied, 
"To give food, and to greet everyone, whether you know or you do not."  <strong>(Bukhari & Muslim) </strong>
</Hadith>
          
<Hadith>
Narrated Abu Huraira: Allah's Apostle (Sallallahu 'Alaihi Wa Sallam) said, "The worst of all mankind is the double-faced one, who comes to some people with one
countenance and to others, with another countenance." <strong>[Bukhari]</strong>
</Hadith>

</text>  